Guide to the Love Makes a Family Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Administrative Files, 1991-2010; Series I
  - Executive Director
    - Topical files
      - Paper
        - Legislative Efforts
          - Miscellaneous opposition, 2000-2009 (Box 8, Folder 9)
            - The Family Institute of Connecticut Highlights 2003, 1
              - Use copy, 1 (Box 30U)
          - Opposition polling, 2005 March (Box 8, Folder 10)
          - LMF Report on Family Institute of Connecticut; press release, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 11)
          - Family Institute of Connecticut Report, "The Case for Same-Sex Marriage in CT", 2002 (Box 8, Folder 12)
          - FIC 990s, 1999-2001 (Box 8, Folder 13)
          - Iowa marriage decision, 2009 April (Box 8, Folder 14)
          - Iowa Amicus briefs, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 15)
          - Gill et al v. OPM, 2009 March (Box 9, Folder 1)
          - Connecticut Commission on Human Rights and Opportunities (CHRO) Salvation Army Petition, 2008 April (Box 9, Folder 2)
          - Kerrigan
            - Supreme Court decision, 2008 October (Box 9, Folder 3)
            - Plaintiffs brief, 2006 November (Box 9, Folder 4)
            - Civil Rights Amicus brief, 2006 December (Box 9, Folder 5)
            - State Supreme Court brief, 2007 February (Box 9, Folder 6)
            - Miscellaneous documents, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 7)
            - Trial Court Ruling, 2006 July (Box 9, Folder 8)
            - Amicus brief Trial Court, 2005 July (Box 9, Folder 9)
            - Motion for Summary Judgment, 2005 July (Box 9, Folder 10)
            - Trial Court brief from the state Attorney General, 2005 November (Box 9, Folder 11)
            - Amicus brief: Family Institute of Connecticut, 2005 November (Box 9, Folder 12)
          - California Marriage decision, 2008 May (Box 10, Folder 1)
          - Cote-Whitacre v. MA DPH, 2006 March (Box 10, Folder 2)
          - New Jersey Supreme Court decision, 2006 October (Box 10, Folder 3)
          - New Jersey APA Amicus brief, 2004 October (Box 10, Folder 4)
          - New York Marriage decision, 2006 July (Box 10, Folder 5)
          - Washington Marriage decision, 2006 July (Box 10, Folder 6)
          - Lawrence v. Texas, 2003 June (Box 10, Folder 7)
          - Goodridge v. Dept of Public Health marriage decision, 2003 November (Box 10, Folder 8)
          - Goodridge Advisory Opinion, 2004 February (Box 10, Folder 9)
          - Baker v. Vermont marriage decision, 1999 December (Box 10, Folder 10)
          - Polls
            - Quinnipiac, 2007 February (Box 11, Folder 1)
            - 2006 polling by Peter Hart Research Associates, 2006 September (Box 11, Folder 2)
              - Data, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 1)
            - Quinnipiac Polling, 2004-2005 (Box 11, Folder 3-4)
            - University of Connecticut marriage poll
              - 2004/CT, 2004 April (Box 11, Folder 5)
              - 2004/New England, 2004 March (Box 11, Folder 6)
            - Quinnipiac University, 2003 October (Box 11, Folder 7)
          - Decision Research
            - Original Proposal from Decision Research for Connecticut polling, 2003 January (Box 11, Folder 8)
            - Poll summary results, 2003 November (Box 11, Folder 9)
            - Poll crosstabs, 2003 November (Box 11, Folder 10)
            - Connecticut Statewide Survey Report, 2003
          - University of Connecticut on marriage/relationship recognition, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 11)
        - Constitutional Convention; PAC
          - Constitutional Convention Campaign, 2007-2008 (Box 11, Folder 12-13)
          - Campaign finance issues, 2007-2008 (Box 11, Folder 14)
          - 2006 LMF PAC (Box 11, Folder 15)
          - 2006 LMF PAC Annual Report (Box 11, Folder 16)
          - PAC Field Plan 2006 (Box 11, Folder 17)
          - Candidate questionnaires
            - Endorsed Senate candidates, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 1)
            - Endorsed House candidates, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 2)
            - Other Senate, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 3)
            - Other House, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 4)
            - Incomplete, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 5)
          - Other organizations' questionnaires, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 6)
          - Constitutional officers questionnaires, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 7)
          - PAC 2003-2004 (Box 12, Folder 8)
          - PAC 2002 (Box 12, Folder 9)
          - Original PAC filings, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 10)
        - Fundraising Materials
          - Grants
            - Anne S. Richardson Fund, 2005-2008 (Box 12, Folder 11)
            - Astraea Foundation, 2002-2007 (Box 12, Folder 12)
            - Asylum Hill Congregational Church, 2003-2006 (Box 12, Folder 13)
            - Carpenter Foundation, 2009 (Box 12, Folder 14)
            - Civil Marriage Collaborative 2008 (Box 12, Folder 15)
            - Civil Marriage Collaborative, 2004-2007 (Box 13, Folder 1-4)
            - Congregational Church in South Glastonbury, 2003-2005 (Box 13, Folder 5)
            - Darmac Foundation, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 6)
            - Fleet Bank PRIDE Foundation, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 7)
            - Freedom to Marry, 2003-2009 (Box 13, Folder 8)
            - Gill Action Fund, 2006-2009 (Box 13, Folder 9)
            - Gill Foundation, 2002-2008 (Box 13, Folder 10-13)
            - Haymarket People's Fund, 2000-2003 (Box 13, Folder 14)
            - Hartford Foundation, Circa 2008-2009 (Box 14, Folder 1)
            - Human Rights Campaign (HRC), 2000-2004 (Box 14, Folder 2)
            - State Equality Fund, 2008-2009 (Box 14, Folder 3)
            - National Gay and Lesbian Task Force (NGLTF), 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 4)
            - Unitarian Universalist Funding program, 2003-2009 (Box 14, Folder 5)
            - Unitarian Universalist Veatch Program, 2003-2008 (Box 14, Folder 6)
          - Events
            - General, printed materials, 2002-2008 (Box 14, Folder 7)
            - Litchfield event, 2004 October 2 (Box 14, Folder 8)
          - Direct mail, 2000-2009 (Box 14, Folder 9)
          - Community Works, 2006-2007 (Box 14, Folder 10)
          - Love Makes a Family Foundation donor packet, 2006 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Associate Director
    - Email correspondence (electronic), Computer files.
      - 2006 Eat Drink and Be Married!, 2005-2006
      - 2007 public hearing testimony
      - 2008 Blog ad campaign
      - 2008 Public Hearing Testimony
      - 2009 Eat, Drink, and Be Married
      - 2009 GIE public hearing testimony
      - 2009 Public Hearing Testimony SB 899 Codification Bill
      - Civil Union Law, 2005-2007
      - CT Clergy for Marriage Equality, 2008-2009
      - Defense of Marriage Act (DOMA), 2009-2010
      - E-mails from other LGBT state orgs, 2004-2009
      - Events and fundraisers, 2005-2009
      - Field Organizing, 2009
      - LMF Action Alerts to Members, 2004-2009
      - LMF PAC emails to members, 2004-2009
      - Maine No on 1, 2009
      - Marriage Makes a Word of Difference film, 2007-2008
      - Media, 2003-2009
      - Opponents E-mail alerts, 2006-2009
      - Pictures, 2005-2009
      - Public Education, 2004-2009
      - Response to Kerrigan decision, 2008
      - Steering Committee-Board, 2004-2009
      - Transplantations theater production, 2007-2009
      - Women and Wine Fundraisers, 2006-2008
    - Topical files
      - Electronic, Computer files.
        - 2007 public hearing testimony
        - 2008 public hearing testimony
        - Bylaws, 2004
        - Cable Access Project 2007, 2007-2008
        - Celebrate the Love Fundraiser 10.1.05, 2005
        - Chapter Coordinators, 2003
        - Congressional District Map_files, 2005 June 14
        - CT CLergy for Marriage Equality, 2003-2008
        - Eat, Drink, Be Married, 2003-2009
        - Educational Outreach, 2005-2009
        - Events Marketing Materials, 2004-2008
        - Fundraisers, 2002-2009
        - House meetings and lobbying, 2003-2009
        - Leadership Summit Master Lists 2006-2007, 2006-2009
        - Letters and Alerts and Directions, 2003-2009
        - LMF Advertisements for Program Books, 2005-2009
        - LMF Brochure, 2002-2004
        - LMF Forums and rally, 2003-2004
        - LMF Logos, 2003-2008
        - LMF Speeches, 2003-2009
        - Marriage Makes a Word of Difference film, 2007-2009
        - Media and Supporting orgs, 2004-2009
        - Media Response Team, 2004-2009
        - PAC 2004-2007, 2004-2009
        - Printing original mailer files, 2005-2009
        - Same Sex Married Couples in CT through June 2009, 2009 December 4
        - Speaker's Bureau, 2005-2009
        - Testimonies hearing 2.7.05, 2005
        - Trans Plantations Theater Production 2008, 2007-2008
        - Transgender Organizing, 2008-2009
        - Volunteers, 2004-2007
        - Website, 2007
        - Youth for Marriage Equality, 2006-2007
      - Paper
        - Connecticut Clergy for Marriage Equality, 2005-2007 (Box 16, Folder 1)
        - Covering LGBT issues in the media, 2005-2006 (Box 16, Folder 2)
        - Fundraisers
          - Printed materials, 2000-2009 (Box 16, Folder 3)
          - Eat, Drink, and Be Married, planning, 2003-2009 (Box 16, Folder 4-8)
        - Family Institute of Connecticut, 2004-2009 (Box 16, Folder 9)
        - Gay & Lesbian Advocates and Defenders (GLAD)
          - "Connecticut Civil Unions", 2005 October (Box 16, Folder 10)
          - "How to Get Married in Connecticut", 2009 May (Box 16, Folder 10)
          - Defense Of Marriage Act challenge: Gill case, 2009 (Box 16, Folder 11)
        - Gay Rights Bill Connecticut, news clippings, 2009 (Box 16, Folder 12)
          Consists of photocopies of a letter from Betty Hudson and newspaper clippings on Connecticut's anti-discrimination bill.
        - Kerrigan case
          - Press kit, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 1)
          - "Decision Day" planning, 2007-2008 (Box 17, Folder 2)
          - Legal documents, 2004-2008 (Box 17, Folder 3-5)
        - Leadership Summit training materials, 2006-2007 (Box 17, Folder 6-8)
        - Legislator House Meetings summaries, 2004-2006 (Box 18, Folder 1)
        - Lobbying, 2006-2008 (Box 21, Folder 3)
        - Lobby Day, 2004, 2007 (Box 18, Folder 2-3)
        - Marriage Makes a Word of Difference, 2007-2008 (Box 18, Folder 4)
          Consists of notes on the the making of the film, a project of the LMF Foundation. The film was directed by Fran Rzeznik and produced by Carol Buckheit.
        - Messaging and strategy from MAP (Movement Advancement Project), 2006-2009 (Box 18, Folder 5-6)
          - Additional materials, 2007, 2009 (Box 20, Folder 1)
        - Press releases and media advisories, 2005-2009 (Box 18, Folder 7)
        - Printed materials, 2004-2009 (Box 18, Folder 8)
          Consists of flyers, postcards, cards, invitations, brochures for various events, fundraisers, and forums.
        - Steering Committee meetings, 2002-2006 (Box 18, Folder 9)
        - Talk by Carol Buckheit, "Media Advocacy and Community Organizing", 2008 (Box 19, Folder 1)
        - Testimonies, Judicial Committee hearings, 2005-2008 (Box 19, Folder 2-4)
        - Trans Plantations, theater production, 2008 (Box 19, Folder 5)
          Consists of material concerning Trans Plantations, a one-woman play starring Janis Astor del Valle about LGBT issues, including marriage equality, in the Latino/a community.
  - Field Organizers, topical files
    - Electronic, Computer files.
      - Decision Day docs Kerrigan case, 2007-2009
      - Eat, Drink, and Be Married, 2007-2009
      - Fact Sheets, 2005-2009
      - Field Organizer Staff Notes
        - Adam Nicholson, Field Director notes, 2005-2009
        - Anthony Gilkes, Community Organizer Notes, 2006-2007
        - Cari Bohm, Community Organizer Notes, 2007-2008
        - Yamuna Menon, Community Organizer notes, 2006-2007
      - House meeting Lists and Organizing 2007-2009, 2006-2008
      - Job Postings, 2007-2008
      - Kerrigan case, 2006-2007
      - Labor 2007, 2007-2008
      - Marriage Judiciary Cmte Postcards 3.25.09, 2009
    - Paper
      - 2009 Connecticut Legislative Guide (Box 22, Folder 1)
      - 2009-2010 Connecticut General Assembly Directory (Box 22, Folder 2)
      - Election data, 2006-2008 (Box 22, Folder 3)
      - Field counts and reports, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 4)
      - Lobby Day and public hearing, Love Makes a Family, 2005 (Box 22, Folder 5)
      - Lobby Day, Connecticut Anti-Discrimination Coalition, Circa 2008-2009 (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - "Meeting your Legislator about Marriage...", 2007-2008 (Box 22, Folder 7)
      - Meeting/speaking notes, 2008-2009 (Box 22, Folder 8)
      - Polling sites, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 9)
      - Printed material, Undated (Box 22, Folder 10)
      - Support Marriage Equality, training material, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 11)
      - Vote No Coalition, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Religious Organizers
    - Connecticut Clergy for Marriage Equality
      - General, 2005-2009 (Box 23, Folder 1)
      - Denomination lists, 2008-2009 (Box 23, Folder 2)
      - Towns
        - Andover, Ansonia, Bloomfield, Branford, 2008 (Box 23, Folder 3)
        - Bridgeport, 2008-2009 (Box 23, Folder 4)
        - Bristol, Chester, Danbury, 2008 (Box 23, Folder 5)
        - Darien, Deep River, Derby, Essex, 2008 (Box 23, Folder 6)
        - Fairfield, 2008 (Box 23, Folder 7)
        - Farmington, Glastonbury, Granby, Greenwich, Groton (and Noank), 2008 (Box 23, Folder 8)
        - Hartford, 2008-2009 (Box 23, Folder 9)
        - Hamden, Higganum, Madison, 2008-2009 (Box 23, Folder 10)
        - Mansfield Center, Meriden, Middlebury, Middletown, Milford, Manchester, New Britain, 2008-2009 (Box 23, Folder 11)
        - New Haven, 2008-2009 (Box 23, Folder 12)
        - Newtown, Niantic, North Haven, Norwalk, Norwich, 2008 (Box 23, Folder 13)
        - Old Lyme, Old Saybrook, Portland, Ridgefield, Riverton, Sharon, South Windsor, Southington, 2009 (Box 23, Folder 14)
        - Stamford, Storrs, Stratford, 2008-2009 (Box 23, Folder 15)
        - Trumbull, Washington, Waterbury, West Hartford, Westport, Windsor, Woodbury, Woodstock, 2008-2009 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Decision Day, 2008 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Faith Action, 2008-2009 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Legislative counts and maps, 2008 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Sample publications, 2008 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Staff meetings, 2008-2009 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Transgender anti-discrimination bill, 2008 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Transgender resources, 2008-2009 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Transgender faith resources, 2008-2009 (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - Vote No Coalition, Circa 2008 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Financial records, 2001-2009 (Box 24, Folder 1-4)
  - Printed material by and about Love Makes a Family
    - News clippings, 2002-2009 (Box 25, Folder 1-8)
    - "Love Makes A Family: The LMF Testimonial Book", 2003 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Victory! Free to Marry in Connecticut, [2008] (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Banner (Box 28)
    - Posters, Circa 2005-2009 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - General resource files
    - Same-sex couples and marriage, reports, 2004-2008 (Box 26, Folder 3-4)
    - Same-sex marriage, Connecticut Bar Association forum, 2004 (Box 27, Folder 1-2)
    - Transgender advocacy, Circa 2007-2009 (Box 27, Folder 3-4)
    - "Volunteer Recruitment Materials Packet," National Gay and Lesbian Task Force, Undated (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Audiovisual Recordings and Photographs, 2001-2009; Series II
  The series, consisting of audiovisual recordings and photographs, richly documents presentations, interviews, rallies, press conferences and other LMF events. It includes LMF produced films and copies of Judiciary Committee hearings on same-sex marriage.
  Many of the events documented in Series II are also documented in Series I, Administrative Files. Researchers interested in a particular event should consult the listings for both series.
  Series II is arranged chronologically by event or publication date.
  Original audiovisual materials, as well as preservation and duplicating masters, may not be played. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist must pay for a use copy, which is retained by the repository. Researchers wishing to obtain an additional copy for their personal use should consult Copying Services information on the Manuscripts and Archives Web site.
  Copies of commercially produced audiovisual materials contained in this collection cannot be made for researcher use outside of the repository.
  - Audiovisual recordings
    Original audiovisual materials, as well as preservation and duplicating masters, may not be played. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist must pay for a use copy, which is retained by the repository. Researchers wishing to obtain an additional copy for their personal use should consult Copying Services information on the Manuscripts and Archives web site.
    - 2000 Vice-presidential Debate, discussion on same-sex marriage, 1 (Box 31)
    - "Vermont Civil Union...Is Connecticut Next", 2001 January 30; 1 (Box 32)
      Forum on same sex marriage organized by Love Makes a Family and held at Wesleyan University.
      - Use copy, 1 (Box 32U)
    - Fox News program, with segment on Love Makes a Family hearing [commercially produced], [2001] March 16; 1 (Box 33)
    - Roundtable, Civil Union, 2001 April; 1 (Box 34)
    - "On the Record: Marriage for Same -Sex Couples," CPTV [commercially produced], 2001 April 1; 1 (Box 35)
    - "Educational Forum on Legal Equality for Same Gender Couples", 2001 November; 1 (Box 36)
      - Use copy, 1 (Box 36U)
    - "Legal Equality for Same-Gender Couples", [2001-2002]; 1 (Box 37)
      Filmed by Betsy Burleson.
    - "Educational Forum on Legal Equality for Same-Gender Couples", 2002 April 10; 1 (Box 38)
      - Use copy, 1 (Box 38U)
    - "The Joe Raia Show" [commercially produced], 2002 November 13; 1 (Box 39)
    - Pro-rally and DOMA rally; LMF press conference; Mike Lawlor, Judiciary co-chair, 2003 January 29; 1 (Box 40)
    - Pro-rally Bushnell; DOMA rally; pro-gay rally, LMF press conference; Mike Lawlor interview, 2003 January 29; 1 (Box 41)
    - "On the Record" [commercially produced], 2003 February 2; 1 (Box 42)
      "On the Record" program recording end abruptly after 1 hour, 1 minutes. Another recorded program continues from this point.
    - LMF Press Conference and Judiciary Committee, 2003 February 24; 1 (Box 43)
    - Capital Lecture Series: Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual and Transgender Relationships, 2003 April 24; 1 (Box 44)
    - Clergy press conference at Legislative Office Building, 2003 April 28; 1 (Box 45)
    - Love Makes a Family Speakout, 2004 February; 8
      - Use copy, 1 (Box 46U)
    - Latinas and Latinos For Marriage Equality press conference, 2004 April; 7
      - Use copy, 1 (Box 47U)
    - "Brass & Words: Westminster, Emerson, Selders, Dyton" [commercially produced], 2004; 27 (Box 48U)
    - "Same Sex Marriage Judiciary Public Hearing" (Connecticut Network) [commercially produced], 2005 February 7; 18
      - Use copy, 2 (Box 49U–50U)
    - "Judiciary Committee Public Hearing and Meeting" (Connecticut Network) [commercially produced], 2005 February 23; 9
      - Use copy, 1 (Box 51U)
    - "CT Judiciary Committee Highlights Speaking for Marriage Equality February 23, 2005", 2005 March 8; 6
      - Use copy, 1 (Box 52U)
    - "Civil Unions Senate" (Connecticut Network) [commercially produced], 2005 April 6; 5
      - Use copy, 1 (Box 53U)
    - "CT House of Representative April 13 Session" (Connecticut Network) [commercially produced], 2005 April 13; 18
      - Use copy, 2 (Box 54U–55U)
    - "CT State Senate April 20 Session" (Connecticut Network) [commercially produced], 2005 April 20; 9
      - Use copy, 1 (Box 56U)
    - "LMF: Civil Union 101 with Maureen M. Murphy Attorney at Law", 2005 July 20; 10
      - Use copy, 1 (Box 57U)
    - Emerson Brass benefit concert [commercially produced], 2005 November 06; 35
      The benefit concert was held at Immanuel Congregational Church in Hartford, Connecticut.
      - Use copy, 2 (Box 58U–59U)
    - Voices in the Wilderness: "Same Gender Marriage" [commercially produced], Circa 2005-2009; 1 (Box 60)
      Program hosted by Rev. Dr. Lorraine Bouffard, with guests Anne Stanback, Teresa Lawrence, and Jeff Carstens.
    - Emerson Brass benefit concert [commercially produced], 2006 October 22
      - Use copy, 1 (Box 61U)
    - "Capitol News Briefing with the Chairs of the Judiciary Committee on Same Sex Marriage Bill" (Connecticut Network) [commercially produced], 2007 January 31; 8
      - Use copy, 1 (Box 62U)
    - "Capitol News Briefing with the Chairs of the Judiciary Committee on Same Sex Marriage Bill" (Connecticut Network) [commercially produced], 2007 March 12; 1 (Box 63)
    - "Judicial Committee Public Hearing" (Connecticut Network) [commercially produced], 2007 March 26; 30
      - Use copy, 3 (Box 64U–66U)
    - "Judiciary Committee Meeting to Take Final Action on Bills" (Connecticut Network) [commercially produced], 2007 Arp 12; 10
      - Use copy, 1 (Box 67U)
    - "CT House of representatives April 13 Session" (Connecticut Network) [commercially produced], 2007 April 13; 1 (Box 68)
    - "Supreme Court Oral Argument: Kerrigan et al. v. The Commissioner of Public Health" (Connecticut Network) [commercially produced], 2007 May 14; 10
      - Use copy, 1 (Box 69U)
    - "Capitol News Briefings Following Supreme Court Arguments of Kerrigan v. Department of Public Health Case" (Connecticut Network) [commercially produced], 2007 May 14; 6
      - Use copy, 1 (Box 70U)
    - Marriage Equality, [2007]; 1 (Box 71)
      Possibly the original recording for "Marriage Equality: Will Connecticut be Next?".
    - "Marriage Equality: Will Connecticut be Next?", 2007
      Versions differ in format and in length.
      - Version 1, 1; 27 minutes; Original videotape damaged; repared during digitization (March 2018). (Box 72)
      - Version 2, 1; 28:45 minutes; Original videotape damaged; repared during digitization (March 2018). (Box 73)
      - Version 3, 7; 66 minutes
        - Use copy, 1 (Box 74U)
    - Interview clips LMF, 2007; 6
      - Use copy, 1 (Box 75U)
    - Peck, Janet, "Speech at Church", Circa 2007; 7
      - Use copy, 1 (Box 76U)
    - Marriage Makes a Word of Difference, 2008; 9
      - Use copy 1 (Box 77U1)
        A film by Fran Rzeznik, Produced by Love Makes a Family.
      - Use copy 2, 1 (Box 77U2)
    - "Judiciary Committee Meeting to Approve Bills & Public Hearing" (Connecticut Network) [commercially produced], 2008 March 17; 30
      - Use copy, 3 (Box 78U–80U)
    - Decision Day in the Kerrigan Case, 2008 October 10
      - Part 1, 8
        Consists of recording of afternoon press conference at the Hartford Hilton Hotel featuring GLAD attorneys and plaintiffs.
        - Use copy, 1 (Box 81U)
      - Part 2
        Consists of a recording of 5pm rally at the State Capitol in Hartford.
        - Use copy, 1 (Box 82U)
    - Love Makes a Family radio interviews on "OutQ in the Morning with Larry Flick" [commercially produced], 2008 October 13; 1
      - Use copy, 1 (Box 83U)
    - Johnston, Brianna, transgender discrimination interviews, 2009 February 12; 9
      - Use copy, 1 (Box 84U)
    - Love Makes a Family Farewell Video: Anne's Version, 2009 June; 7
      - Use copy, 1 (Box 85U)
    - Long, Gannon interview on Metrocast, Waterford Cable, 2009 October; 7
      Long discusses transgender issues.
      - Use copy, 1 (Box 86U)
    - Buckheit, Carol interview on Metrocast, Waterford Cable, 2009 October 19; 7
      Buckheit discusses closure of Love Makes a Family.
      - Use copy, 1 (Box 87U)
    - First Anniversary of Marriage Equality in Connecticut at State Capital, 2009 November 12; 8
      - Use copy, 1 (Box 88U)
    - Love Makes a Family Farewell Video, 2009 November 13; 7
      - Use copy, 1 (Box 89U)